expresspakistan.net 2012-09-16

# Privacy Policy ~ Expressing Pakistan - Expresspakistan.net

Our privacy policy describes how expresspakistan.net uses and protects any information given when visiting this website.

**Collection of Information:  **

Expresspakistan.net is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement, Except for authorized law enforcement investigations. Expresspakistan.net collects information from our users at several different points on our website. No individual information about any visitor will be released to any third party without that visitors permission. The information collected will be used in the aggregate only and is for the sole internal use of expresspakistan.net.﻿

**Log Files:  **

Like many other Web sites, expresspakistan.net makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**E-mail Newsletters:**

If users wish to subscribe to our e-mail newsletters, we ask for contact information. Our Daily Newsletter is powered by FeedBurner, however we use in-house solution for weekly Newsletter. We/Feedburner use information submitted by you in the same manner as we use contact information described above. Recipients of our newsletters can unsubscribe using the instructions listed at the end of the e-mail newsletter.

**Website Traffic Analysis Software:**

For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, we employ software programs to monitor traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. We also monitor our traffic to analyze visitors’s information, such as, but not limited to, operating system, browsers, screen resolutions and similar.

In the event of authorized law enforcement investigations, and pursuant to any required legal process, information from these sources may be used to help identify an individual.

**Cookies:**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on expresspakistan.net.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to expresspakistan.net and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include:

**Google Adsense**

Registration: In order to use some features of our website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest.

**Security:  **

In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure any information collected online.

**Links to other websites:  **

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. Whilst efforts are made to ensure that the links included are valid, we cannot be held responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide once you have left this site. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question
